fsw.edu 2018-10-04

# Privacy Policy | Florida SouthWestern State College

* * *

Thank you for visiting the Florida SouthWestern State College website. Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, our policy is to collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us.

When you visit our website, our Web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed our website. This information does not result in the identification of your personal email address or other personal information.

In addition, we gather information regarding the volume and timing of access to our website by collecting information on the date, time and website pages accessed by visitors to the website. We do this so we can improve the content of our website, and this information is not shared with other organizations. Again, only aggregate information is collected, and individual visitors' personal information is not identified.

If you choose to share personal information with us - by sending us a message or by filling out an electronic form with personal information - we will use the information only for the purpose you authorized. Some of the information may be saved for a designated period of time to comply with Florida's archiving policies, but we will not disclose the information to third parties or other governmental agencies, unless required or authorized to do so by state or federal law.

**Notice of Collection, Use and Release of Social Security Numbers**

Under Florida law, e-mail addresses are public records. By entering your email address on any form or document on this website, it is possible for your email address to be released in response to an official public records request. If you do not want your e-mail address released in a specific situation, please call the appropriate department at the college. We use email addresses only for their intended purpose and do not give them out unless required by law.

If you have any questions about our privacy policies, or have ideas about improving our policies, please feel free to contact us at [webmaster@fsw.edu](mailto:webmaster@fsw.edu)
